真不敢相信我加了她
I couldn't believe I had done it.
是一瞬间的疯狂 还是本能地想要自我毁灭?
Was it a moment of madness or an attempt at self-destruction?
我不确定
I wasn't sure.
我有好几次想删除好友 却又阻止了自己
I went to unfriend her many times, but I always stopped myself.
她是真的有病 还是被人误解 每个故事都有两面
She is ill, misunderstood. There are two sides to every story.
倘若生活本就浑浑噩噩 单凭某个人就能将它彻底摧毁吗?
If you aren't living a life worth living, then can someone ruin it at all?
然后她开始 在我的所有照片下添加评论
Then came the comments on all my photos,
有些甚至是我刚注册账户时上传的
some as far back as when I first opened the account.
在我和前女友琪莉的合影旁 发表酸溜溜的评论
Jealous remarks on photos with my ex-girlfriend Keeley,
还用奇怪的文字描述我的一举一动
alongside these bizarre captions describing my every move.
饥渴的小驯鹿
运动小驯鹿
淘气小鹿
开心的小驯鹿
玛莎·史考特
在吗?
今晚太浪漫拉 驯鹿
我门算正式交往了吗?
玛莎 那不是约会 那只是...
你岗在打字?怎么停下了?
有人在你傍边吗?
小驯鹿 你根别人在一起吗?
你没有回达我的问题 驯鹿宝贝
从我的iPhone发送
《驯鹿宝贝》
托尼 不管你在玩什么花样 你成功吸引了我的注意
Well, Tony, whatever you're doing, it's working.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我只是说
I'm just saying,
我们已经见过六次了
we've met six times now.
你每次都是讲完一堆笑话就早早离开
All you do is crack jokes then leave early.
通常女生都会感觉受到了羞辱
A girl should be insulted,
但可恨的是 这样反而勾起了我的兴趣
but I hate that it intrigues me.
我喜欢慢慢来 在这方面我是个绅士
Well, I like to take it slow. I'm a gentleman in that respect.
你从不送我去地铁站 不和我谈论你的生活
You never walk me to the Tube. You never tell me about your life.
也不用脸书
You're not on Facebook.
我无从分辨你是否真诚
I can't tell if you're genuine
会不会哪天我一觉醒来 发现自己被绑架或者谋杀了?
or I'm gonna wake up one day inside a true-crime podcast.
好吧 你想知道些什么?
Well, what do you wanna know?
告诉我你为什么总是坚持要来这里
Tell me why you always insist on coming here.
原因有很多 比如这里氛围好
Well, lots of reasons. Great atmosphere.
是啊 评判一间酒吧的好坏
Yes, you can always judge a great bar
只要看里面有多少人 在读《金融时报》就够了
by how many people are reading the Financial Times.
而且这里光线太暗了 我一整晚只能眯缝着眼看你
It's so dark too. I feel all I do is squint at you all evening.
那就别眯眼 任眼神迷离
Ah, well, don't squint, then. Just let your eyes fuzz.
我在朦胧的视线中更能进入状态
I really come into my own when I'm in a soft focus.
你真的很奇怪
You're so weird.
- 是吗? - 没关系 奇怪很好 我喜欢
- Am I? - It's fine. I like weird.
或多或少 人人都有各自的古怪 大家都在扮演着正常人
We're all varying degrees of weird, aren't we? Pretending to be human.
说得好 真好 对 我可以借鉴
Ah, that's good, that is. Yeah, I'll use that.
富有哲理的话 在工地上很受欢迎是吗 托尼?
Philosophy go down well on the construction site, does it, Tony?
我是在跨性别交友网站上认识的泰瑞
I met Teri by signing up to a trans dating website.
作为伪装 我把名字从唐尼改成了托尼
I changed my name from Donny to Tony
还虚构了一份工作 把自己包装成另一个人
and invented a job and an entire persona as a means of keeping myself disguised.
我痛恨此等行径
I hated myself for doing it,
但又实在不想 被人发现我注册了那个网站
but I just couldn't bear the thought of anyone finding out.
我从没想过会坠入爱河
I never expected to fall in love.
- 你好 - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
她聪颖 风趣 有激情 无所顾忌地展现自我
She was brilliant. Fierce, witty, unashamed.
她拥有我所不具备的一切
Everything I was not.
她是一名治疗师 六年前移居伦敦
A therapist who moved to London six years ago
目前在市中心工作
and was now working in the heart of the city.
随着一次次地聊天 大笑 一起消磨时间到天亮
The more we laughed and chatted and wound down the clock until morning,
我越来越为她着迷
the more and more I fell for her.
当你跟某人说话时
You know something's right
会激动到头皮发麻 便会意识到那是对的人
when you get that tingly feeling behind your eyes when you talk to them.
可一想到假如跟她约会时 遇见我认识的人
But then I would think about bumping into someone I knew together,
比如酒吧或者喜剧界的人
from the pub or from the comedy world,
而他们看出来 我在跟一个跨性别女性约会
that they could tell somehow that I was dating a trans woman,
我会羞耻到恨不得找个地缝钻进去
and I just couldn't move past the bullshit of my shame.
所以每次出去约会
So when it came to meeting outside,
我都会把地点约在城市边缘 一间昏暗的鸡尾酒吧
I kept our dates to a dim cocktail bar on the edge of town.
怎么
Well,
托尼
Tony,
不打算说点什么吗?
are you gonna say something?
我一直想坦白 我其实不叫托尼
I always meant to tell her about Tony,
但我越是喜欢她 就越拖着不敢开口
but the more I fell for her, the more I found myself putting it off.
你为什么不回达我的问题?
从我的iPhone发送
发送至泰瑞 昨晚约会很愉快 周五老地方见?
你在这儿呀 弗兰基宝贝
There he is. Frankie, baby.
玛莎
Martha. Um...
- 你好 - 老实说
- Uh, hi.- Honestly,
你昨晚去哪儿了? 你不上班的话该告诉我呀
where were you last night? You need to tell me if you're not working.
害我一直担心你会不会 死在了运河里 脸朝下漂在水上
Kept thinking of you floating in that canal somewhere, face down.
就是你走去坐公车时 要经过的那条运河
The one you go through when you walk to the bus from work.
那条路有很多奇怪的人 瘾君子 小偷 什么人都有
All sorts of weird fuckers down that way. Junkies and thieves. All kinds.
还有很多亚洲人
Asians.
你得小心呀
- You should be careful. - Uh...
天哪 对了 我很喜欢你的脸书页面
Oh my God, been loving your Facebook page by the way.
只是我想不通 你怎么老爱跟那些荡妇瞎混
Don't know what I think of the tarts you surround yourself with.
尤其是那个琪莉·利赫
That Keeley Leigh one in particular.
她总爱抱着你 把鼻子埋进你的后颈
The way she's always hugging you and burrowing her nose into your nape.
那女人是有多饥渴呀?
I mean, how desperate can one tart be?
简直难以置信
Can you imagine it?
你在给谁发短信?
So, who are you texting?
- 你说什么? - 不是那个叫琪莉的贱人吧?
- I'm sorry? - Wasn't that Keeley bint, was it?
不是 玛莎 你要真想知道 琪莉只是我的一个老朋友
No, Martha. If you must know, Keeley's just an old friend, okay?
男女之间没有纯粹的友谊
Men and women can't be friends.
你们是炮友?
You fucking her?
什么? 不 玛莎 我们不是 拜托你别纠结这个话题了 好吗?
What? No, Martha, I'm not. Now, will you drop it, please?
天啊 对不起 小驯鹿
Oh my God. I'm sorry, reindeer.
吓着你了吧 我知道 是我太激动了
I'm a nightmare, I know. I was getting carried away with myself.
我只是不太擅长竞争 知道吗?
I'm just not very good with competition, see?
它会害我展现出最坏的一面
Tends to bring out the worst in me.
- 怎么说? - 表现在很多方面
- How so? - Oh, lots of ways, really.
我会沉迷在网上 查找所有关于情敌的信息
I find myself getting lost on the Internet trying to find out everything about them.
不过别担心 小驯鹿 我知道你是单身
But don't worry, reindeer. I know you're single.
你不会在追求我的同时 还跟一个妖艳贱货纠缠不清
You don't sing into a girl's soul like that with a tart on the side.
那样太残忍了
That'd be cruel.
我不会接受的
I wouldn't abide by that.
总之 我们进屋再说吧
Anyway, I'll get you inside.
那晚我失眠了 我害怕玛莎发现泰瑞的事
I couldn't sleep that night for fear of Martha finding out about Teri.
我们换个地方 去这儿吧
到时会怎样?
What would happen then?
我对自己发誓 要尽可能地让她俩保持距离
I made a vow to keep them as far apart as possible.
我以为让泰瑞远离玛莎 会比较容易实现
I figured the easier thing to do would be to keep Teri away from Martha.
嘿 泰瑞
Hey, Teri!
你怎么来了?
What are you doing here?
天啊
Holy shit.
光今天就有几百封邮件
There's, like, hundreds just today.
你全看过吗?
Have you read all these?
没有 一天时间根本看不过来
No, there's not enough time in the day to read all of them.
其中有些内容...
Some of these are...
她显然精神不太正常
I mean, she's clearly unwell.
是啊 所以我认为 我们应该暂时保持低调
Yeah. That's why I think we should lay low for a while.
她为什么叫你唐尼?
Why does she call you Donny?
她给我起了很多外号
Oh, she... she calls me lots of things. Um...
笑笑骨、小奶头...
Funny bones, nipple-head--
驯鹿宝贝?
Baby reindeer?
她应该不是律师吧
I'm assuming she's not a lawyer.
对 根本不可能 她成天在心跳里干坐着
No, she can't be. Spends all day sitting in the Heart.
心跳? 卡姆登区的那家酒吧?
The Heart? The pub in Camden?
- 我刚才说什么了? - 心跳
- Uh, what did I say? - The Heart.
你是在那遇见她的?
Is that where you met?
对 其实我有点记不大清了
yeah, I'm just trying to remember, actually.
卡姆登区就那一家心跳酒吧
Well, there's only one Heart in Camden.
我现在都不敢去了
I don't go there anymore.
你昨天才去过
According to these, you were there yesterday.
我没有 是她瞎编的
I wasn't. She's just lying.
警察怎么说?
What are the police saying to all this?
我觉得这事还不至于...
Oh, I... I don't think it merits...
没那么严重吧
I mean, it's not that bad.
但已经严重到我们需要暂时低调了
But bad enough that we need to lay low for a while.
你为什么不报警?
Why haven't you reported this?
不知道 她只是有点疯疯癫癫的
I don't know. She's just batty.
除了会发些奇怪的邮件 其实并没有对我造成多大困扰
I mean, apart from a few random emails, it really isn't all that much.
我只是不想把你也卷进来
I just didn't wanna drag you into it.
"没多大困扰"?
Not that much?
她有妄想症 给自己幻想出了一个全新的身份
She's a fantasist who's fabricated an entire identity for herself.
这危险信号还不够强烈吗 托尼?
Does that not scream alarm bells, Tony?
不一定吧 人都会出于各种原因说谎
I don't know about that. People lie for all sorts of reasons.
不会说这样的谎
Not like this they don't.
答应我 你会解决这件事
Promise me you'll shut this down.
因为我不会逃避任何人
Because I'm not hiding from anyone.
如果你解决不了 也许我只好到卡姆登区
If you don't, I might have to come to Camden
去找她当面说了
and pay her a visit myself.
整件事宛如一场噩梦 每一个谎言和错误的决定
It was like some crazy nightmare, where each lie and wrong decision
都莫名地拉近着玛莎和泰瑞的距离
somehow bound Martha and Teri closer together.
仿佛在冥冥之中
Like the universe was punishing me
每当我想要全身而退时 都会遭到上天的惩罚
every single time I tried to cower my way out of the situation.
天哪 小奶头
Jeezo, nipple!
我在这里为你担心15分钟了
Fifteen minutes I've been here worrying my head off about you.
说真的 你要迟到的话 得先跟我打个招呼呀
Honestly! You need to tell me when you're running late.
至少把你的电话号码给我吧 我就不用干着急了
At least give me your goddamn phone number so I won't have to worry so much.
来吧 你知道该怎么做 小奶头
Come on, you know the drill, nipple.
快给我来杯健怡可乐喝喝 然后我就得走了
Quick Diet Coke to wet the whistle, and I'll be offski.
两块五英镑 谢谢
£2.50, please.
- 你从来不收我钱的 - 我必须收
- You never charge me. - I have to.
- 我买不起 - 你不是律师吗?
- I can't afford it. - Thought you were a lawyer, no?
你今天怎么这么奇怪?
What you being weird for?
我没有 只是我觉得 咱俩是时候划清界限了
I'm not. I just think it's time we drew a few boundaries.
你说过会满足我的需求
You said about the curtains.
我知道 那是在开玩笑 我是个喜剧人 就爱开玩笑
I know. That was a joke. I'm a comedian. I make jokes.
什么? 所以...
What? So...
你和我之间的一切...都只是个玩笑?
this has all been... one big wind-up, has it?
疯女人玛莎 自作聪明 结果小丑竟是我?
Crazy Martha... with her big brain. Joke's on her?
不 不是那样的
No, no, it's... it's not like that.
你说过好多撩我的话 小驯鹿
You've said a lot of shit to me, reindeer.
不 玛莎 请你别哭
Yeah. No, Martha, uh, please don't cry.
什么?
What?
你是说对我从来就没感觉吗?
Are you saying you've never had feelings for me?
不 很显然 我没那么说
No. No, I'm not saying that, obviously.
我觉得你很好 只是...
I think you're... great. It's just...
只是什么?
What is it?
- 是什么? - 年龄差距
- Well, what is it? - The age gap.
但我们的年龄差距不算太大呀
But there's not that much of an age gap.
对 但等我想要孩子
Yeah, but by the time I want kids,
想要一个大家庭时 问题就大了
you know, like a big family, it's... it's... it's gonna matter.
确实会有点麻烦
Oh, that'd be tricky.
是啊
Yeah.
这个该死的世界
This fucking world.
就只会肆无忌惮地索取
All it does is take from you.
经血从我的阴道凶涌而出 一大堆黏乎乎的东西
医生说我的卵子 好象20岁女生的一样哦
你响什么时候来播种呀?
从我的iPhone发送
那一晚 玛莎的邮件疯狂涌入 一封接一封地
That night, Martha flooded my account with email after email
细数着她的月经 卫生棉条 血块
detailing periods, tampons, blood clots,
强调她旺盛的生育能力
reinforcing this image of her fertility.
在她眼里 我已没有任何理由推开她了
There was no excuse now, in her eyes.
我们俨然就要确定关系
We were becoming a thing.
快点 小驯鹿
Quick! Reindeer!
快呀 开门
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Open!
现在每天早上 玛莎都会在
Every morning now, Martha would arrive
开店前两小时赶到
exactly two hours before the pub opened.
然后在酒吧待一整天 跟在我屁股后头
Then all day she would trail me around the bar,
无休止地畅谈着我们的未来
talking endlessly about our future together.
我仔细考虑过了 我愿意
I've thought hard about it, and my answer's yes.
- 愿意什么? - 跟你结婚生子 生一大堆
- Yes to what? - Kids, marriage, the full nine yards.
我从来没说过要跟你结婚
I never said anything about marriage.
无论我去哪里 她都会出现
Everywhere I turned, she just seemed to be there,
在最不合时宜的时刻蹦出来 谈论我们的未来
popping up at the most inopportune moments to talk about our future together.
我们的婚礼 要给孩子取什么名字...
Our wedding day, what we were gonna call our kids...
只要抓紧时间 我应该能生三个
I think I can do three if we move quickly.
我连孩子的名字都想好了 你看
I've even been thinking of what to call them too. Here.
...那个画面让我不寒而栗 几乎跟她选的名字一样可怕
...the image of which horrified me almost as much as the names she'd chosen.
爱格伯特-基斯-尼奥
我试着疏远她
I tried to distance myself,
但她依旧执迷不悟 一门心思缠着我
but she still persevered with the same dead-eyed commitment.
- 需要帮忙吗 弗兰基宝贝? - 不用
- Need a hand, Frankie baby? - What? No, I'm fine.
喜欢我叫你"弗兰基宝贝"吗?
Do you like that? "Frankie baby"?
取自双人组合成员弗兰基·辛纳特拉 他也有迷人的翘臀
From the duet. Frankie Sinatra. He had a gorgeous tush too.
我手里拿着热腾腾的餐食呢
I've got hot fucking plates in my hand.
- 你能别围着我转了吗? - 我买好半决赛的门票了
- Will you stop fussing around me? - I've got tickets to the semifinal.
什么?
What?
你比赛的门票 我会去为你助阵的
Tickets. For your competition. Gonna come down and empty my lungs.
我最近在学一首对唱曲目 这次我想唱凯莉和杰森的歌
Been learning a new duet too. I'm thinking Kylie and Jason this time.
- 你要来看比赛? - 当然
- You're coming to the competition? - Absolutely.
我还想着等半决赛结束了 跟你来场全垒打呢
And I thought, after your semi, I could give you a full erection.
我们得禁止玛莎入店
We need to bar Martha.
什么? 不可能
What? No chance.
那我们这一整年的笑料都没了
That'd be like barring a year's worth of banter.
说实在的 唐尼 没了她 你简直无聊透顶
Let's be honest, Donny. You're nothing without her.
听我说 好吗? 吉诺 请你出去一下
Just hear me out. Gino, can you leave?
不 你想跟我说什么 都可以当着我老婆的面说
No. What you can say in front of me, you can say in front of the missus.
听着 我有种不好的预感
Look, I'm just getting a bad feeling.
瞧瞧她发给我的这堆邮件 你看
I mean, look at all these emails she's been sending me. Here.
天哪 见鬼 这也太离谱了吧
Oh man. Oh, shit, man. That's... That is proper nuts.
- 现在明白了吧? - 我也拿不准
- Get my point? - I don't know.
这年头要禁止某人进店是很复杂的
Barring is complicated these days.
若没有实证 我们很可能引火烧身
Unless you've got evidence, it can come back on us.
- 她怎么会知道你的邮箱? - 这不重要
- How'd she get your email? - It doesn't matter.
重点是她知道了我的邮箱
All that matters is she did get it,
现在我们有充分的证据 禁止她进店 不是吗?
and now we have all the evidence we need to bar her, right?
证据确实不少 这条你看过了吗?
There's plenty of evidence here. You read this one?
不是吧 那也太野蛮了
Oh no. No, that... that is brutal.
- 哪一条? - 你求她跟你肛交那条
- Which one is that? - The one where you beg her for anal sex.
- 你胡说什么呢? - 你看
- What are you talking about? - Here.
在我看来 你似乎一直在求她跟你肛交啊
Looks to me like you've been begging her for anal sex, mate.
你回信了 你他妈在逗我吗?
You wrote back. Are you fucking kidding me?
跟我肛交吧
可恶 你居然发过去了
Shit, you actually sent it.
你傻吗? 你他妈是白痴吗?
Are you stupid? Are you a fucking moron?
冷静点 她只会把这当笑话看
Oh, chill. She'll see it as a joke.
什么时候?
在哪里?
从我的iPhone发送
简直难以置信
It was incredible, really,
一切正以惊人的速度滑向崩溃的边缘
just how quickly things seemed to be falling apart.
你好 请问是杰森吗?
Hi, is that Jason?
你好 是的 我是唐尼
Hi, yeah, yeah, yeah. It's Donny. I'm just, um...
很抱歉这么晚打电话过来
I... I'm sorry to call so late.
请问能不能 把我半决赛的日期改到另一天?
I'm just wondering if I can move my semifinal to the other date?
对 我得处理一些家事 目前的日期我恐怕来不了
Yeah, I have to tend to some family shit, which means I can't do the current one.
天啊 你真是我的英雄
Oh man, you're a hero!
非常感谢 杰哥 我能叫你杰哥吗?
Thanks, Jase. Can I call you Jase?
好的 谢谢你 杰森 再见 伙计 再见
All right. Thanks, Jason. Bye, mate. Bye.
哇 你做到了
wow! You made it.
我特意选了一个同性恋酒吧 想看你会不会受不了
I picked the gayest bar intentionally just to see if you'd crack.
我知道 那我该怎么办? 要避免吸入空气中的微粒吗?
I know you did. So what do I do? Do I avoid breathing in the air particles?
别闹了
Oh, shut up!
你总能领会这种讽刺性的幽默 真好 否则你还挺让人受不了的
You'd be pretty damn intolerable if you didn't get irony.
- 我就当你是在夸我了 - 就是在夸你
- I'll take that as a compliment. - Mmm, you should.
我有同意你搂我的腰吗?
Did I give you consent to put your arms around my waist?
你有 你穿着这条 性感小裙子来赴约 就等于默许了
You did, actually, when you turned up in that skimpy little dress.
你还没喝就醉了吗?
Are you drunk already?
爱让我迷醉
Ah, just on love.
少来
Oh, go away.
真的 改天让你见见我的女神
I'm serious. You should meet her someday.
天啊 我超爱这首歌 来 我们去跳舞吧
Oh my God, I fucking love this song. Come on, let's dance. Let's dance.
- 我没想到你还会跳舞 - 我不会啊 但我要把你拖下水
- I didn't have you down as a dancer. - I'm not but I'll drag you down with me.
说真的 你怎么像变了个人似的 托尼去哪儿了?
Honestly, what have you done with him? Where's Tony?
我是他的双胞胎弟弟 他让我来替他把你拿下
I'm his twin. He sends me to seal the deal for him.
好吧 告诉他这是违法的
Well, tell him that's illegal.
什么违法?
What is?
用假身份跟人上床
Sleeping with someone under a false identity.
是吗?
Is it?
当然
Yeah, of course.
那你叫什么名字 双胞胎弟弟?
What's your name, then, twinny?
唐尼
Donny.
奇怪 玛莎就是这么叫你的
Weird. That's what Martha calls you.
是啊...
Yeah, um...
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
嗯 那个 我需要...
Yeah. Yeah. Um, tell you what, let me just, um...
失陪一下 好吗?
One second, yeah?
真他妈见鬼
Fuck's sake!
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
没事 我们去喝一杯吧?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I'm fine. Um, shall we get a drink?
你要不还是先缓缓吧
I think you should maybe slow down a bit.
- 好 - 过来 坐下
- Okay. - Here. Sit.
喝点水
Have some water.
可恶
Oh, fuck.
今天是不是出了什么事? 你似乎很困扰
Did something happen to you today? You seem troubled.
不 我没事
No, I'm fine.
不会是玛莎吧?
Martha, by any chance?
直觉告诉我 这事一定很有意思
Something tells me I'm gonna enjoy this.
不 我只是...我想婉转地拒绝她
No, I just, um... I thought I'd let her down gently
所以编了个借口说我想要孩子
by making out that I wanted kids and stuff.
真是越来越有趣了
Oh, this gets better and better.
- 想知道我的想法吗? - 我想不想你都会照说不误吧
- Do you wanna know what I think? - I think you're gonna tell me anyway.
我觉得你乐在其中
I think you're enjoying this.
你只不过读了几封邮件而已 别一副洞察一切的样子
You've read a few emails. Stop acting like you know the situation.
我用谷歌搜索过她
You know, I googled her.
你为什么没告诉我她以前坐过牢?
Why didn't you tell me that she'd been to jail before?
我感觉那无关紧要
Didn't seem relevant.
明白我的意思了吧?
See what I mean?
任何一个理智清醒的人 被有暴力倾向的前科犯盯上
Any sane person who was getting stalked by a violent ex-convict
都会毫不犹豫地报警
wouldn't hesitate to go to the police.
但你没有
But not you.
在你看来 她人畜无害
To you, she's harmless.
在你看来 她值得同情
To you, she's sympathetic.
在你看来 她坐过牢无关紧要?
To you, it's not relevant?
我只是想说 你之所以让她 一直缠着你不放 是有原因的
I'm just saying, there's a reason you're keeping her around,
也许重点不在于她是谁
and maybe it's not so much who she is, .
而在于她能给予你什么
but..what she gives you.
因为 敞开了说吧
Because let's be honest,
被人一厢情愿单恋的感觉 实在太舒适了
love is most comforting, isn't it, when it's felt one way.
不然你以为我为什么会在这里?
Why else do you think I'm here?
你就是个大骗子
You're a tremendous liar.
今晚跟我回家吧
Come back with me tonight.
只是别告诉托尼
Just don't tell Tony.
好
Okay.
小驯鹿 你在哪? 你不能撩完人家就玩失宗
从我的iPhone发送
有时候当你编织出一张谎言的巨网
Sometimes you create such a web of lies that you almost forget
会几乎忘了 自己一开始想要逃离的是什么
what you started running from in the first place.
但此刻我站在这里 眼前是我的梦中情人
But here I was, the woman of my dreams before me,
建筑师托尼 还差四站就要踏上性犯罪的不归路
Tony the builder, four stops away from a sex crime.
天啊
Oh my God.
没想到我喝得这么醉
I'm way drunker than I thought I was.
可气的是 偏偏我现在恢复清醒了
Annoyingly, just as my sobriety returns.
天啊 真抱歉
Oh my God, I'm so sorry!
站着别乱晃 好吗?
Just keep still, will you?
我好像踩到了一个老太太
I think I just stepped on an old lady.
小声点 好吗?
Just... just keep it down a bit, yeah?
你顾虑太多了
You care too much.
我不鼓励嗑药 但我觉得那或许对你有好处
I don't encourage drug addiction, but I think it might be good for you.
来 把手给我
Here, give me your hands.
你造房子时会换一双手吗?
When you do your building work, do you put a new set of hands on?
什么意思?
What do you mean?
它们不像建筑工人那种布满老茧的手
It's just they're not very calloused for a builder.
这双是我的自慰专用手 我每天都把它们和工作手换着用
Oh, these are my wanking hands. I swap them round every day.
你试过用长满老茧的手自慰吗?
You ever tried wanking with calloused hands?
我还挺期待的
I was rather looking forward to it.
你要怎样才肯好好吻我一下?
What's it gonna take for you to finally give me a proper kiss?
抱歉 你说什么?
Sorry, what was that?
吻我
Kiss me.
本以为我是个积极主动的人 却发现我骨子里是个懦夫
It is so devastating to think of yourself as a progressive person,
泰瑞来电
那打击简直令人崩溃
only to realize you're a coward underneath it all.
但当你花费漫长的时间 消化内心的羞耻
But when you spend so long swallowing your shame,
它会不可避免地转化为你的一部分
it is so hard to stop it becoming part of you.
你这小色鬼
You filthy fucker.
我从来没跟人肛交过 但为了你 我愿意妥协
I've never taken it up the chufter, but I might make concessions for you.
求你了 玛莎 我只想回家
Please, Martha. I just need to go home.
你得二选一哦 小帅哥
You got a choice, boy.
是想要孩子还是欢乐肛交
Kids or bum fun.
我不知道法夫的综合学校 是怎么教的生理课
'Cause I don't know what they taught you in those Fife comprehensives,
但靠肛交是没法生小孩的
but if you stick it in the two, then you don't get the 2.4.
- 懂我的意思吗? - 玛莎 拜托你回家吧
- Do you know what I mean? - Martha, just go back home.
我真的很烦你这套 犹豫不决 忽冷忽热的把戏
You're really getting on my nerves with this dilly-dally, hot-and-cold shit!
- 让开 玛莎 - 不让
- Get out of my way, Martha. No!
我已经把心给了你
I've already given parts of myself away to you.
你要想推开我 至少该给我一个解释
So the least you can do is piece me back together
让我对你死心吧?
with some bloody justification.
我告诉你 你最好考虑清楚
Because let me tell you this for size.
看不上我的男人
Men who don't fancy me
不是眼瞎就是同性恋
are either blind or gay.
我可没见你爬楼梯时去摸索扶手
I don't see you reaching for the banister when you climb the stairs.
我他妈的才不是同性恋 玛莎 天哪
No, I'm not fucking gay, Martha. Jesus.
那就别再推开我了
Then stop pushing me away.
我可以帮你的 知道吗?
I can help you, you know?
帮我什么?
Help with what?
那个人
The person.
- 伤害了你的人 - 我不知道你在说什么
- The one that hurt you. - I don't know what you're talking about.
那是个男人 对吧?
It was a man, wasn't it?
他对你做了什么?
What did he do to you?
好了 我要走了 好吧?
Okay, I'm just gonna leave, yeah?
我现在转身走开 你不要跟上来
I'm just gonna turn and walk away, and you're not to follow.
听明白了吗?
Do you understand?
很好
Good.
我没跟你开玩笑 玛莎
I'm not playing here, Martha.
你就是在玩 月月先生 抓到喽
Yes, you are, Mr. Blobby. Tag!
- 你他妈在干什么? - 喜欢吗? 月月先生
- What the fuck are you doing? - Do you like it? Mr. Blobby.
我是月月夫人 因为我一直来月经
I'm Mrs. Blobby 'cause I'm always on the blob.
- 抓到啦  - 别碰我
- Tag! - Get off me.
- 抓到了哦 - 滚开
- Tag! - Fuck off.
- 抓到你啦 - 我是认真的 玛莎 别碰我
- Tag! - I'm serious, Martha. Get off me!
我没心情跟你玩 管好你的手
I'm not messing here. Keep your hands to yourself.
真他妈的要命
Jesus fucking Christ.
天哪 我是认真的 玛莎 别闹了
Oh, fuck's sake. I'm serious, Martha. Stop right now.
离我远点
Fucking back off!
玛莎
Martha
玛莎 你在干什么?
Martha, what are you doing?
- 抓到啦 - 搞什么?
- Tag! - What the fuck?
- 抓到了 - 我叫你住手
- Tag! - I told you to stop!
玛莎 我跟你说真的 别乱摸
Martha, I'm serious. Keep your fucking hands to yourself.
- 见鬼... - 抓住了
- Fuck off-- - Tag!
玛莎 等等 住手
Martha, wait. Just stop.
别动
Keep still.
你的心在怦怦跳
You're beating.
我让你心动了
I'm making you beat.
根据理查德·加德的话剧 《驯鹿宝贝》改编